Guide to the Kristine Stiles Collection, 1900-[ongoing] RL.01254
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Name files, 42 boxes
  - Balkenhol, Stephan, 1998 (Box 132)
  - Balka, Miroslaw, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Ballatore, Sandy, 1981 (Box 132)
  - Bamgboyé, Oladélé Ajibayé, 1999 (Box 132)
  - Banana, Anna, 2004-2011 (Box 132)
  - Banff New Media Institute, 1999 (Box 133)
  - BANK, 1998-2002 (Box 133)
  - Bard College, 1999 (Box 133)
  - Bargaoanu, Alina, 2001 (Box 133)
  - Barney, Matthew (Box 133)
  - Barolsky, Paul, 1988-1998 (Box 133)
  - Barraclough, David, 1974 (Box 133)
  - Barry, Bob, 1978 (Box 133)
  - Barry, Judith, 1977-1979 (Box 133)
  - Barry, Kathy, 1993 (Box 133)
  - Bartos, Robert, 1994 (Box 133)
  - Baselitz, 2001 (Box 133)
  - Basis Wren, 1997 (Box 133)
  - Bass, Needham, 2008 (Box 133)
  - Basualdo, Carlos, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Bleistein, Susan, 2014 (Box 214)
  - Blier, Suzanne, 2015 (Box 214)
  - Becker, Jack, 1994 (Box 133)
  - Beesch, Ruth, 1996-2005 (Box 133)
  - Bejan, Adrian, 1992-2007 (Box 133)
  - Beke, Laszlo, 2001 (Box 133)
  - Bélas, Tilless, 1998\ (Box 133)
  - Bellerjeau, Harriet, 1992 (Box 133)
  - Below, Max (Rada Dada) (Box 133)
  - Benayoun, Maurice (2006-2009) (Box 133)
  - Benton, Suzanne, 1995 (Box 133)
  - Benayoun, Maurice (2006-2009) (Box 133)
  - Berg, Adam, 1980 (Box 133)
  - Berger, Maurice, 1989-1998 (Box 133)
  - Berghaus, Günter, 2001 (Box 133)
  - Berke, Joseph, 2008 (Box 133)
  - Berner, Jeff, 1987-1993 (Box 133)
  - Berry, Jocelyn, 1994 (Box 133)
  - Bertalan, Stefan (Box 133)
  - Bessire, Mark H.C., 2002 (Box 133)
  - Betterton, Rosemary, 2001 (Box 133)
  - Beuys, Eva, 1986 (Box 133)
  - Beuys, Joseph, 1982 (Box 133)
  - Bidlo, Mike, 1998 (Box 133)
  - Bielstein, Susan, 2002-2008 (Box 133)
  - Bierman, Noah, 1995 (Box 133)
  - Bing, Xu, 2000 (Box 133)
  - Bireline, George, 2005 (Box 133)
  - Bireline, Jennie, 1993-2008 (Box 133)
  - Black Dog Publishing, 2001 (Box 133)
  - Blackwell, Christine, 2009 (Box 133)
  - Blackwell, Jonathan, 2003 (Box 133)
  - Blaine, Julien, 1968-2000 (Box 133)
  - Bland, Kalman, 2000 (Box 133)
  - Blandiana, Anna, 1997 (Box 133)
  - Blâdu, Mihail (Box 133)
  - Blank, Harrod, 1995 (Box 133)
  - Blank, Shoshana, 1998 (Box 133)
  - Blasthaus, 1996 (Box 133)
  - Blazwick, Iwona, 2003 (Box 134)
  - Bleecher, Stephanie, 1989 (Box 134)
  - Blocker, Jane, 2002 (Box 134)
  - Bloom, Jay, 2004 (Box 134)
  - Bloom, James, 2007 (Box 134)
  - Blue Skies, 1991 (Box 134)
  - Bochner, Mel, 1993-2001 (Box 134)
  - Boettger, Suzaan, 2000 (Box 134)
  - Bogner, Dieter, 1996 (Box 134)
  - Bojan, Maria Rus, 1997-2009 (Box 134)
  - Bollinger, Rebecca, 1997 (Box 134)
  - Bonk, Ecke, 2009 (Box 134)
  - Boresta, Pino, 1998-2000 (Box 134)
  - Borte, Elena, 1993 (Box 134)
  - Bosland, Joost, 2007 (Box 134)
  - Bostic, Connie, 2000 (Box 134)
  - Bound and Unbound (Box 134)
  - Bourgoin, Marisa, 2007 (Box 134)
  - Bourodimos, Angela, 1991-1999 (Box 134)
  - Bowman, John, 2003 (Box 134)
  - Bowron, E. Peters, 1994 (Box 134)
  - Boyce, Sonia, 2001 (Box 134)
  - Boyers, Lowell, 2004-2007 (Box 134)
  - Brakhage, Marilyn, 2008 (Box 134)
  - Brakhage, Stan (Box 134)
  - Braila, Pavel, 1999 (Box 134)
  - Brancusi, Constantin, 1995 (Box 134)
  - Braverman, Robert, 1991 (Box 134)
  - Brecht, George, 1978-2005 (Box 134)
    - Interview with George Brecht Tape 1 (Box 134, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0021, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0021_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0021_02.wav)
    - Interview with George Brecht Tape 2 (Box 134, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0022, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0022_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0022_02.wav)
    - Interview with George Brecht Tape 3 (Box 134, Audio-cassette RL01254-CS-0023, Digital-materials RL01254-SET-0002, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0023_01.wav, Audio-file RL01254-CS-0023_02.wav)
  - Brendel, János, 1997 (Box 134)
  - Brett, Guy, 1996-1998 (Box 134)
  - Brisley, Stuart, 1980-2002 (Box 134)
  - Broadcast (Box 134)
  - Broderson, Deborah, 1999 (Box 134)
  - Brodhead, Richard H., 2011 (Box 134)
  - Brodie, Russell Garrett, 2009 (Box 135)
  - Brody, Jennifer and Sharon Holland (Box 135)
  - Brody's Gallery (Judy and Tom Brody) (Box 135)
  - Broodthaers, Marcle, 1997 (Box 135)
  - Brooks, Adam, 1993 (Box 135)
  - Broom, Bill, 2003 (Box 135)
  - Brown, Christopher, 1992-1998 (Box 135)
  - Brown, David, 2000 (Box 135)
  - Brown, Joan, 1994 (Box 135)
  - Brown, Kathan, 1977 (Box 135)
  - Bruch, Kathy, 1990 (Box 135)
  - Brud, Jan, 1997 (Box 135)
  - Brueske, Judith, 1989 (Box 135)
  - Brunet, Lynn, 2005-2007 (Box 135)
  - Brus, Günter, 1989-1998 (Box 135)
  - Bruzelius, Caroline (Box 135)
  - Buchanan, Nancy, 2000 (Box 135)
  - Bucharest University/Duke University Student and Faculty Exchange Program, 1993 (Box 135)
  - Bukoff, Allen, 1994-1995 (Box 135)
  - Burden, Chris, 1979-1994 (Box 135)
  - Burger, Jodi, 2001 (Box 135)
  - Burness, John, 2005 (Box 135)
  - Burnham, Jack, 1977 (Box 135)
  - Burnham, Linda, 1985-2001 (Box 135)
  - Burns, Clara Marie, 2001 (Box 135)
  - Burns, Jeff, 2002 (Box 135)
  - Byrd, Charles, 2006 (Box 135)
  - Byrd, Jeffery, 1998 (Box 135)
  - Bullock, Nate, 2012 (Box 214)
  - Byrne, Blake, 2012 (Box 135)
  - C ART E, Special Edition, 15 May - 6 June, 1994, On the Book (Box 135)
  - Cabañas, Kaira, 1998-2003 (Box 135)
  - Cage, John, 1992 (Box 135)
  - Cairoli, Patricia, 2007 (Box 135)
  - Calle, Sophie, 1998 (Box 135)
  - Candau, Eugenia "Genie", 1979-1996 (Box 135)
  - Cardiff, Janet (Box 135)
  - Cârneci, Magda, 1997 (Box 135)
  - Carrión, Ulises, 1978-1981 (Box 135)
  - Carroll, Amy, 2001 (Box 135)
  - Carroll, Noël (Box 135)
  - Carson, Gary, 2009-2015 (Box 135)
  - Carson and Miller, 2009 (Box 135)
  - Cassilly, Ellen (Box 135)
  - Cassouto, Nella, 1994 (Box 135)
  - Castillon, Roland, 1983-1984 (Box 135)
  - Catlett, Elizabeth, 2001 (Box 135)
  - Cavallaro, Cosimo (Box 135)
  - Daris, Gabriella, 2015 (Box 214)
  - Cecelski, David, 2004 (Box 135)
  - Cenizas, 1982-1983 (Box 135)
  - Center for Metamedia (Box 135)
  - Cernuschi, Claude, 1997 (Box 136)
  - Cavellini, Guglielmo Achille, 2014 (Box 214)
  - Cha, Theresa Hak Kyung, 1980-2001 (Box 136)
  - Carver, Stuart, 2015 (Box 214)
  - Chadwick, Whitney, 1984 (Box 136)
  - Chafe, William, 2000 (Box 136)
  - Chagoya, Enrique, 2004 (Box 136)
  - Chametzky, Peter, 1997 (Box 136)
  - Chandler, Annmarie, 2002 (Box 136)
  - Chelimsky, Oscar, 1985 (Box 136)
  - Cheng, Meiling, 1997-2002 (Box 136)
  - Chiari, Giuseppe (Box 136)
  - Chicago, Judy, 2000-2005 (Box 136)
  - Chin, Mel, 2004 (Box 136)
  - Choi, Jung E., 2013 (Box 214)
  - Chan, Irene, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Chopin, Henri, 1981-2006 (Box 136)
  - Choueiri, Ginou, 2010 (Box 136)
  - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 1989 (Box 136)
  - Chung, David, 1998-2000 (Box 136)
  - Cibulka, Heinz, photographs from installation/performance, Vienna, 1979 (Box 136)
  - Cios, Irina, 1995 (Box 136)
  - Clarke, John, R., 1991 (Box 136)
  - Clavez, Bertrand, 2002 (Box 136)
  - Clemente, Francesco, 1988 (Box 136)
  - Cleveland Performance Art Festival, 1998-1999 (Box 136)
  - Close, Chuck (Box 136)
  - Clum, John, 2007 (Box 136)
  - Clutton, Robert, 1969 (Box 136)
  - Cobbing, Bob, 1982-1983 (Box 136)
  - Codrescu, Andrei, 1993-2009 (Box 136)
  - Coffey, John, 1995 (Box 136)
  - Cohen, Sorel, 1981 (Box 136)
  - Cojocaru, Eugen, 1993 (Box 136)
  - Collector's Choice, 2000 (Box 136)
  - Collins, Bradford, 2002 (Box 136)
  - Comanescu, Denisa, 1992 (Box 136)
  - Comfort Zone, 2002 (Box 136)
  - Concannon, Kevin, 1997-2000 (Box 136)
  - Conner, Jean, 2013-2014 (Box 214)
  - Conner, Bruce, 1956-2012 (Box 136)
  - Conners, Callè, 1994 (Box 136)
  - Connolly, Brian, 2002 (Box 137)
  - Constantinescu, Emil, 1992 (Box 137)
  - Contemporary Arab Representation, Beirut, Lebanon, 2002 (Box 137)
  - Conz, Francesco, 1992-2000 (Box 137)
  - Cooke, Lynne, 1993 (Box 137)
  - Cooke, Miriam, 2001-2009 (Box 137)
  - Cormack, Sarah, 1998 (Box 137)
  - Corn, Wanda, 1987 (Box 137)
  - Cornilescu, Alexandra, 1992-2003 (Box 137)
  - Corris, Michael, 1999-2009 (2 folders) (Box 137)
  - Cortez, Diego, 1999 (Box 137)
  - Cosey Fanni Tutti, 1998 (Box 137)
  - Costa, Anthony, 2001 (Box 137)
  - Costinas, Cosmin, 2006 (Box 137)
  - Cottingham, Laura, 2002-2009 (Box 137)
  - Couillard, Paul, 2008 (Box 137)
  - Coyne, Petah, 2005 (Box 137)
  - Cracknell, Andrew, 1981 (Box 137)
  - Craven, James B., III, 2005-2009 (Box 137)
  - Cresenzo, Rick, 2008 (Box 137)
  - Critical Arts Ensemble, 2005 (Box 137)
  - Critical Mass, 2000 (Box 137)
  - Croatia (Box 137)
  - Cronin, Christopher, 1992 (Box 137)
  - Crosson, Courtney, 2004-2005 (Box 137)
  - Crow, Thomas, 1999 (Box 137)
  - Crumbliss, Alvin, 2010-2011 (Box 138)
  - Cuban Performance Art of the 1980s, 1998 (Box 138)
  - Culler, Jeremy, 2002 (Box 138)
  - Curley, Jay, 1997-2011 (Box 138)
  - Cutts, Simon, 1989-1990 (Box 138)
  - D.C. Space publication (Box 138)
  - Dachy, Mare, 1996 (Box 138)
  - d'Agostino, Peter, 1979-2011 (Box 138)
  - Dal Poggetto, Lynne, 1997 (Box 138)
  - Dance Theater Workshop/The Suitcase Fund, 1993 (Box 138)
  - Datuin, Flaudette May, 2006 (Box 138)
  - Daucikova, Anna, 1998 (Box 138)
  - Davidson, Bruce, 1992 (Box 138)
  - Davidson, Cathy, 2000-2008 (Box 138)
  - Davidson, Karen, 1992-2003 (Box 138)
  - Davies, Ivor, 1986-2010 (Box 138)
  - Deakin, Simon, 2012-2015 (Box 214)
  - Davies, Penny, 1983 (Box 138)
  - Dávila, Mela, 2003 (Box 138)
  - Davis, Gregson, 2007 (Box 138)
  - De Dominicis, Gino, 1999 (Box 138)
  - de Vos, Katherine, 2000-2013 (Box 138, Box 214)
  - de Monchaux, Cathy, 2000 (Box 138)
  - Dea n's Award for Excellence in Mentoring, 2011 (Box 138)
  - Décimo, Marc (Box 138)
  - DeFeo, Jay, 1990-1996 (Box 138)
  - Dempsey, Terrence, 1993 (Box 138)
  - Dent, Even, 2000 (Box 138)
  - DePillars, Murry, 1993 (Box 138)
  - Deyhle, Juliane, 1975 (Box 138)
  - Di Giulio, Margaret Eller, 2008 (Box 138)
  - "Dialogue on New Arts" talk by Kristine Stiles for "The 60s Theories of Reality," Walker Art Center, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1983 (Box 138)
  - Diaz, Lope Max, 1995 (Box 138)
  - Dickens, Denise, 1994-1995 (Box 138)
  - Dickens, Sarah Jones, 2007-2015 (Box 138, Box 214)
  - Dietrich, Linn, 2000 (Box 138)
  - Dillard, Sherrie (Box 138)
  - Dillon, Jennifer, 2008 (Box 138)
  - Dine, Jim, 2000 (Box 138)
  - Dion, Mark, 2004 (Box 138)
  - Dippel, Rini, 1983 (Box 138)
  - DJ Spooky, 2002 (Box 138)
  - Doha, Qatar (Box 138)
  - Doll, Nancy M., 2001 (Box 138)
  - Donahue, Joseph, 2014 (Box 214)
  - Donovan, Kathleen, 2000 (Box 138)
  - Dougherty, Patrick, 2012 (Box 214)
  - Dougherty, Cecilia, 1998 (Box 138)
  - Dougherty, Molly, 2002 (Box 138)
  - Dougherty, Patrick (Box 139)
  - Dragan, Anatoli (Dr.) (Box 139)
  - Drake, James, 1997 (Box 139)
  - Dreher, Thomas, 1995-2002 (Box 139)
  - Dreyblatt, Arnold, 1993-2008 (Box 139)
  - Drotos, Frederica, 1993 (Box 139)
  - Druckrey, Timothy, 1999 (Box 139)
  - Dudding, George (Box 139)
  - du Pont, Diana C., 1999 (Box 139)
  - Duffy, Alec Nathan, 2001 (Box 139)
  - Duke University/Cornell University Curatorial Consortium, Venice Biennale, 2011 (Box 139)
  - Duke University Library Special Collections, 2009 (Box 139)
  - Duke University Women Studies, 2011 (Box 139)
  - Dumitrescu, Zamfir, 1988 (Box 139)
  - Duncan, John, 1997-2009 (Box 139)
  - Dunning, Jeanne, 1989 (Box 139)
  - Dunzendorfer, Herwig, 1991 (Box 139)
  - Durham County, 2000 (Box 139)
  - Durham, Jimmie, 2003 (Box 139)
  - Durland, Steven, 1997-2010 (Box 139)
  - Eberle, Clare (Box 139)
  - Echelman, Janet, 2001 (Box 139)
  - Edelson, Mary Beth, 2002 (Box 139)
  - "The Effects of Rap Music on Teens," UNC Wilmington, 1995 (Box 139)
  - Eichhorn, Maria, 2004 (Box 139)
  - Elder, Muldoon (Box 139)
  - Elkins, James and Margaret MacNamidhe, 1995-2009 (Box 139)
  - Elvin, Sylvia, 1991 (Box 139)
  - Ephemera, no. 7 and 9, 1978 (Box 139)
  - The Equitable Gallery, 1995 (Box 139)
  - Ernst, Tess (Box 139)
  - Ernst, Judith, 2009 (Box 139)
  - Eric, Zoran, 1999-2005 (Box 140)
  - Eshleman, Clayton, 2002-2008 (Box 140)
  - Evans, Walker, 1998 (Box 140)
  - Everson, William, 1974 (Box 140)
  - Ex Libris, Museum of Decorative Arts, Prague, Czech Republic (Box 140)
  - Exit Art, Papa Colo and Jeanette Ingberman, 1984-1992 (Box 140)
  - Éxpo-see, 1982-1983 (Box 140)
  - Export, Valie, 1984-2001 (Box 140)
  - "The F Word: Reclaiming Feminism in the Visual Arts," 2007 (Box 140)
  - Fabyc, Deej, 2009 (Box 140)
  - Farganis, Sondra, 1998 (Box 140)
  - Feldman, Ronald, 1992 (Box 140)
  - Ferguson, Russell, 1997-2008 (Box 140)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1974 (Box 140)
  - Fernández, Teresita, 1997-2005 (Box 140)
  - Ferriero, David, 2000-2001 (Box 140)
  - Ffarrabas, Nye, 2002 (Box 140)
  - Fiddy, Michael, 2002 (Box 140)
  - Filippone, Christine, 2007-2009 (Box 140)
  - Filliou, Robert, 1982-1999 (Box 140)
  - Finley, Elizabeth, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Finley, Karen, 1994-2006 (2 folders) (Box 140)
  - Finster, Howard, 1998 (Box 140)
  - First Balkan Biennial, 2005 (Box 140)
  - Fischer, Hervé, 1980-2005 (Box 140)
  - Fischer, Iancua, 1992 (Box 140)
  - Fischer, Yona, 1994 (Box 141)
  - Fisher, Anna, 2007 (Box 141)
  - Fisher, Janet, 2001 (Box 141)
  - Flatz, Wolfgang (Box 141)
  - Fleming, Sherman, 1991-2011 (Box 141)
  - Flondor, Constantin (Box 141)
  - Fluxus, 1984-2003 (Box 141, Box 214)
  - Folsom, Fred, 1992 (Box 141)
  - Fontana, Bill, 2006 (Box 141)
  - Fortin, André, 1980-1981 (Box 141)
  - Fortin, Sylvie, 2000 (Box 141)
  - Fortinberry-Murray Method, 1997 (Box 141)
  - Fox, Faulkner, 2004 (Box 141)
  - Fox, Terry, 1976-2000 (Box 141)
  - France, Michael and Kathleen, 2011 (Box 141)
  - Franklin Furnace (Martha Wilson), 1977-2015 (Box 141, Box 214)
  - Franko, Mark, 2008 (Box 141)
  - Fredrickson, Laurel, 2003 (Box 141)
  - Free International University (Box 141)
  - Friedman, Ken, 1989-2000 (Box 141)
  - Friedman, Lori, 1988 (Box 141)
  - "From Energy to Information: Representation in Science, Art, and Literature," University of Texas at Austin, 1997 (Box 141)
  - Frost, Jerry, 2004 (Box 141)
  - Frueh, Joanna, 1999 (Box 141)
  - Fryd, Vivien Green, 2007 (Box 142)
  - Fundaction Ortiz Gurdian, Leon, Nicaragua, 2003 (Box 142)
  - Furunishi, Noriko, 2009 (Box 142)
  - Fusco, Coco, 1998 (Box 142)
  - Gach, Gary, 1980 (Box 142)
  - Gaines, Kathryn (Box 142)
  - Galántai, György, 1998 (Box 142)
  - Galembo, Phyllis, 1999 (Box 142)
  - Galerie Kruh (Box 142)
  - Garrent, Jonathan C., 2012 (Box 214)
  - Gamboni, Dario, 1995 (Box 142)
  - Garoian, Charles, 1977-2002 (Box 142)
  - Garrett, J.C., 1999-2010 (Box 142)
  - Garruba, Nancy, 1987 (Box 142)
  - Gatewood, Hunter, 1997 (Box 142)
  - Gautherot, Franck, Les Presses du Réel, 1993 (Box 142)
  - General Idea, 2001 (A.A. Bronson, Felix Partz, Jorge Zontal) (Box 142)
  - Gerhard Jaschke, Herausgegeben von, 1999 (Box 142)
  - Gershuni, Moshe (Box 142)
  - Gilbert and George, 2004 (Box 142)
  - Giliberti, Diana, 2005 (Box 142)
  - Gendron, Heather Hope, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Gillette, Frank, 2004 (Box 142)
  - Gilliam, Bryan and Vivian Clark, 2010 (Box 142)
  - Gilliam, Sam, 1998-2009 (Box 142)
  - Gillick, Liam, 2002 (Box 142)
  - Giovanelli, Jean-Pierre, 1979-1987 (Box 142)
  - Gilliam, Stephanie, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Gitlin, Michael, 1994 (Box 142)
  - Gitlin, Todd, 2000 (Box 142)
  - Glass, Philip, 1998 (Box 142)
  - Gleseke, Frank, 1997 (Box 142)
  - Gluck, Bruce, 1987 (Box 142)
  - Goldenberg, Michael (Box 142)
  - Goldman, Saundra, 1995 (Box 142)
  - Goldstein, Joel (Box 142)
  - Goldstein, Malcolm, 1984 (Box 142)
  - Goeritz, Mathias, 1984, undated (Box 214)
  - Goldwater, Marge, 1995-2000 (Box 142)
  - Golec, Michael, J., 1999-2000 (Box 142)
  - Gómez-Peña, Guillermo, 2001 (Box 142)
  - Gonzalez-Torres, Felix, 1994 (Box 142)
  - Gordon, Marsha, 2013-2013 (Box 214)
  - Gordon, Douglas, 2012 (Box 142)
  - Gorduz, Vasile, 1992 (Box 142)
  - Gorsen, Peter (Box 142)
  - Gotovac, Tomislav, 1994 (Box 142)
  - Graham, Dan, 1993-1998 (Box 142)
  - Graham, Lonnie, 1993 (Box 143)
  - Grant, Don, 1983-1993 (Box 143)
  - Grateful Dead T-Shirt, 1971 (Box 143)
  - Gray, John, 1989-1996 (Box 143)
  - Gray, Sam, 2003 (Box 143)
  - Greenberg, Aliza (Box 214)
  - Green, Gregory, 1998 (Box 143)
  - Green, Renée, 1993 (Box 143)
  - Greenewag, Kristen (Box 214)
  - Greene, Balcomb, 1962 (Box 143)
  - Schoonmaker, Trevor, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Gray, Spalding, 1992 (Box 143)
  - White, David, 2014 (Box 214)
  - Griffin, Mary Charles, 2004-2005 (Box 143)
  - Grillo, Benito, 1992 (Box 143)
  - Grimmer, Neil, 1998 (Box 143)
  - Grimshaw, Chloe, 1996 (Box 143)
  - Grimsley, Nancy, 1979 (Box 143)
  - Groothuis, Douglas (Box 214)
  - Grobstein, Paul, 2006 (Box 143)
  - Grusevski, Daniela (Box 143)
  - Schmidt, Bastienne, 2015 (Box 214)
  - Guatemala, Embassay of, 1998 (Box 143)
  - Guerico, Gabriele, 2000 (Box 143)
  - Guerilla Art Action Group, 1970-1997 (Box 143)
  - Guerilla Girls, 1997 (Box 143)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 2000-2008 (Box 143)
  - Guggenheim Museum, 2006-2009 (Box 143)
  - Guomundsson, Guômundur (Ferró Erró), 2004 (Box 143)
  - H.Arta (Maria Crista, Anca Gyemant, and Rodica, Tache) (Box 144)
  - Guta, Adrian, 1993-1996 (Box 144)
  - Haacke, Hans, 1995 (Box 144)
  - Haagen, Paul H., 2007 (Box 144)
  - Hales, Peter (Box 214)
  - Hafftka, Michael, 1996 (Box 144)
  - Halkias, Melanie, 2002 (Box 144)
  - Hall, Doug (Box 144)
  - Halpern, Adrian, 2002 (Box 144)
  - Hamelink, Cees J., 1993 (Box 144)
  - Yau, John, 1988 (Box 202)
  - Silva, Michelle, 2014 (Box 214)
  - Hammersley, Frederick (Box 214)
  - Hamilton, Ann, 1993-2008 (Box 144)
  - Hammond, Deborah, 1997 (Box 144)
  - Hammond, Jane, 1994-2006 (Box 144)
  - Hanart TZ Gallery, 2000 (Box 144)
  - Schroth, Sarah, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Hanas, Erin, 2011 (Box 144)
  - Hannah, David, 1998 (Box 144)
  - Hansen, Al, 2000 (Box 144)
  - Hansen, Bibbe, 1997-2004 (Box 144)
  - Harding, James, 2000-2004 (Box 144)
  - Hardt, Michael, 2001-2009 (Box 144)
  - Harms, Anja and Ines, 1991 (Box 144)
  - Harned, Richard, 1988-1991 (Box 144)
  - Harris, Alex, 2004 (Box 144)
  - Harris, Michael, 1997 (Box 144)
  - Harrison, Charles, 2000-2009 (Box 144)
  - Harsanyi, Poina and Nicolae, 1994 (Box 144)
  - Hartnett, Gerald, 2001 (Box 144)
  - Harrison, Helen and Newton, 1991-1993 (Box 144)
  - Harvey, Emily, 1994 (Box 144)
  - Hassold, Edith, 1992-1995 (Box 144)
  - Hattersley-Smith, Kara, 2009 (Box 144)
  - Hattinger, Gottfried, 1994-1996 (Box 144)
  - Harcourt, Glenn (Box 214)
  - Hart, Emma (Box 214)
  - Hayes, Jay and John, 1983 (Box 144)
  - Haywood, Robert, 1995-2000 (Box 144)
  - Heaton, Kelly (Box 144)
  - Heffernan, Mary Beth, 2005 (Box 144)
  - Heftler, Scott, 2000 (Box 144)
  - Hegyi, Dora, 2008 (Box 144)
  - Heidsieck, Bernard, 1987 (Box 144)
  - Heiman, Michal, 1996 (Box 144)
  - Heinemann, Sue, 2007 (Box 144)
  - Hell, Julia, 1999 (Box 144)
  - Hellmuth, Suzanne and Jock Reynolds, 1995 (Box 144)
  - Hendee, Stephen, 2000 (Box 144)
  - Henderson, Linda D., 1996-2004 (Box 144)
  - Hendricks, Geoffrey, 1980-2000 (Box 145)
  - Hendricks, Jon, 1980-2000 (Box 145)
  - Hendricks, Susan, 2008 (Box 145)
  - Henri (Henrietta Ehrsam), 1986 (Box 145)
  - Henthorn, Cynthia, 1998 (Box 145)
  - Hepworth, Barbara, 1955 (Box 145)
  - Herman, Roger, 1981-2009 (Box 145)
  - Herold, George, 1995 (Box 145)
  - Herold, Jörg, 2005-2007 (Box 145)
  - Herring, Oliver and Leonilson, 1996 (Box 145)
  - Herron, Matt, 1994 (Box 145)
  - Hershman, Lynn 1978-2011 (Box 145)
  - Hershman, Lynn - Kristine Stiles as Roberta Breitmore (Box 145)
  - Hesford, Wendy Sue, 2000 (Box 145)
  - Hess, Nicole, 2006 (Box 145)
  - Hesse, Eva, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Hewitt, Nancy, 1994 (Box 145)
  - Higgins, Chester, 2000 (Box 145)
  - Higgins, Hannah, 1996-2009 (Box 145)
  - Hill, Allison (Box 145)
  - Hill, Henry, 1992 (Box 145)
  - Hill, Nan and Brian Longe (Box 145)
  - Hillings, Valerie (Box 145)
  - Hillman, Susan, 1982 (Box 146)
  - Hirsch, Meyer, 1981 (Box 146)
  - Hirschman, Jack, 2009 (Box 146)
  - Hitchcock, Ned, 1999 (Box 146)
  - Hochdoerfer, Achim, 2002 (Box 146)
  - Hoffman, Ellen (Box 146)
  - Hoare, Jess (Box 214)
  - Holl, Ute, 2005 (Box 146)
  - Hill, Sarah (Box 214)
  - Holloway, Karla, 2000 (Box 146)
  - Hollowell, David, 2000 (Box 146)
  - Holsenback, Bryant, 2005 (Box 146)
  - Holt, Jessica, 1997 (Box 146)
  - Vason, Manuel, 2013 (Box 214)
  - Hong, Yk, 2001 (Box 146)
  - Honey, Martha, 1994-1995 (Box 146)
  - Sanford, Laurie, 2014-2015 (Box 214)
  - Hoover, Dana, 1999 (Box 146)
  - Hornick, Neil, 2008 (Box 146)
  - Horodinca, Vlad, 1998 (Box 146)
  - Horrigan, Bryan (Box 146)
  - Houghton, Charlotte, 2004 (Box 146)
  - House, Lys, 2001 (Box 146)
  - Hsieh, Tehching, 2000 (Box 146)
  - Huan, Zhang, 2000 (Box 146)
  - Hudson, Kathy, 2009 (Box 146)
  - Huffman, Kathy Rae, 1997 (Box 146)
  - Hughes, Holly, 1995-2001 (Box 146)
  - Hugunin, James R., 1999 (Box 146)
  - Hunter, Tim, 1981 (Box 146)
  - Husain, M.F., 2010 (Box 146)
  - Hussong, Randy, 2002-2010 (Box 146)
  - Huyssen, Andreas, 1993 (Box 146)
  - Iagulli, Sergio, 1982-1983 (Box 146)
  - Iles, Chrissie, 1998 (Box 146)
  - Impakt Festival, 1997-1999 (Box 146)
  - "The Incident," Symposium, Fribourg, Sweden, 1995 (Box 146)
  - Ingeborg, Strobol (Box 146)
  - Insam, Grita, 1980 (Box 146)
  - Interlude: Contributions to an International Conference on Peace, Marginalization, Eurocentrism, and Resistance, 1987 (Box 146)
  - Intermedia Arts (Box 146)
  - Ionescu, Dan and Dana (Box 146)
  - Ipomal Galerie en kunstuitleen (Box 146)
  - Ireland, David, 1989-2000 (Box 146)
  - Irimia, Mihaela, 1994 (Box 146)
  - Irwin, Kim, 1992-1998 (Box 146)
  - Irwin, Richard (Box 147)
  - Israel - Miscellaneous (Box 147)
  - isto, Raino (Box 214)
  - Raqs Media Collective, 2003 (Box 214)
  - Israel, Nico, 2002 (Box 147)
  - IT (Box 147)
  - Ivekovic, Sanja (Box 147)
  - Jaar, Alfredo, 1991 (Box 147)
  - Jackson, Jed, 1984-1987 (Box 147)
  - Jakubowska, Agata (Box 214)
  - Jaegers, Bevy, 2001 (Box 147)
  - James B. Duke Society, 2010 (Box 147)
  - James, Danté, 2007 (Box 147)
  - James, David E., 1998 (Box 147)
  - James, Erica, 2001-2008 (Box 147)
  - Janschka, Fritz, 2001-2007 (Box 147)
  - Jarosi, Susan, 2008-2010 (Box 147)
  - Jay, Martin, 1985-2000 (Box 147)
  - Jensen, Rob, 1984-1989 (Box 147)
  - Jeremijenko, Natalie, 2001 (Box 147)
  - Jetelová, Magdalena, 1987 (Box 147)
  - Jet Wave, 1980-1981 (Box 147)
  - Jeu de Paume, 2003 (Box 147)
  - Jewart, Eric, 2001 (Box 147)
  - Johnson, Bridget, 1981 (Box 147)
  - Johnson, Douglas James (Box 147)
  - Johnson, Ray, 1995 (Box 147)
  - Johnston, Jill, 1998 (Box 147)
  - Jonas, Joan (Box 147)
  - Jones, Amelia (Box 147)
  - Jones, Joe, 1994 (Box 147)
  - Jones, Kim, 1993-2011 (Box 147)
  - Jones, Ronald, 1994-1999 (Box 147)
  - Jordan, Teresa, 2006 (Box 147)
  - Jose, Regina, 2008 (Box 147)
  - Joy, Bill, 2000 (Box 148)
  - The Judd Foundation, 1997 (Box 148)
  - Julien, Isaac, 1999-2004 (Box 148)
  - Justensen, Kirsten, 1994-2003 (Box 148)
  - K-ahtic, 1985 (Box 148)
  - Kabakov, Ilya (Box 148)
  - Kac, Eduardo, 200-2004 (Box 148)
  - Kadishman, Menashe, 1972-1978 (Box 148)
  - Kahn, Douglas, 1989-2000 (Box 148)
  - Kamen, Rebecca, 1986-1993 (Box 148)
  - Kantor, Istvan, 2004-2005 (Box 148)
  - Karacsonyt, Boldog, 2004 (Box 148)
  - Karlstrom, Paul, 2010 (Box 148)
  - Kaplan, Roz, 1994 (Box 148)
  - Kapoor, Anish, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Kaponen, Sondra, 1983-1985 (Box 148)
  - Karkowski, Z., 1991 (Box 148)
  - Karp, Ivan (Box 148)
  - Katchka, Kinsey, 2008 (Box 148)
  - Katz, Rebecca, 1985-2009 (Box 148)
  - Katzew, Ilona, 2001 (Box 148)
  - Kato, Yukiko, 2007 (Box 148)
  - Katona-Apte, Judit, 1998 (Box 148)
  - Kelley, Anthony M, 1992-2001 (Box 148)
  - Kelley, Heather Ryan, 1996 (Box 148)
  - Kelley, Maxine, 1999 (Box 148)
  - Kelley, Mike, 1998 (Box 149)
  - Kazmierezak, Malgorzata (Box 214)
  - Kellough, Jim, 1992-2003 (Box 149)